Mom.
I saved Premier Medical Hall.
And I took down the Wang Family.
Dad and Ren Ran
are both doing well.
We all miss you so much.
Oh, and Mom,
Ruo Jin and I
got married.
She also gave you an
incredibly adorable little granddaughter.
Ruo Jin,
come offer incense
for Mom.
No!
You called the police!
I won't let anyone off!
No, no!
Ruo Jin!
It's all my fault!
I'm to blame!
Ruo Jin!
It's all my fault!
I'm a sinner, I deserve to die!
Ruo Jin!
Feifan.
Feifan, it was me.
I got Auntie Ren killed.
I ruined the entire Ren family.
I'm a sinner against the Ren family.
It's all my fault, Feifan.
Ruo Jin.
Ruo Jin, Ruo Jin!
Ruo Jin!
Feifan.
I don't want to leave you.
We finally made it through.
I'm begging you.
Can't you cure anything?
Please save me, Feifan.
Help me.
Please, save me.
Feifan, I'm begging you.
Ruo Jin.
Ruo Jin, look at me.
It's me, Feifan.
None of this is your fault.
It's all over now.
It's not your fault.
None of it has anything to do with you.
Don't blame yourself.
Xu Ruo Jin.
The one who should be in chains
is you.
Listen.
Inside this room,
every footstep is proof of your guilt.
Ruo Jin!
I got on the phone with my mentor.
Professor Andrew sent me some materials.
They're recent overseas cases
of treating similar conditions.
Okay, and then?
I forwarded them to you.
Sent me what?
The case files.
Why send me case files?
What I need is a treatment method.
If necessary,
I can take Ruo Jin to England for treatment.
I told you, it's not that simple.
There are two little people inside Ruo Jin.
Once she's triggered by outside stimuli,
those two little people start fighting.
She's been using her vital energy to keep it in check.
But every time those two fight,
her vital energy takes a serious hit.
If this keeps up,
her body will give out sooner or later.
Out with it.
How did you trigger her this time?
I just took her
to offer incense at my mother's memorial.
Told her the Wang Family had been brought to justice,
and that Ruo Jin and I got married.
Like I just said,
Ruo Jin has two triggers.
One of them is your mother.
When did you ever tell me that?
I just told you.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
So what's the other trigger?
Wang Wenhao.
But Wang Wenhao's already been brought to justice.
But as long as Wang Wenhao lives,
she won't have a moment's peace.
You two, stop arguing! Something's happened.
I just got word.
Wang Wenhao escaped.
What?
He escaped?
Prison break.
Before dying, Wang Chengren bribed two guards.
Wang Wenhao escaped hidden in an ambulance.
He's wanted across the city now.
This is bad.
Young Master Gu,
head to Premier Medical Hall right away.
Take my dad, Ren Ran, and Ruo Jin to your safe house.
I'll pull some strings.
Whatever it takes,
we have to find Wang Wenhao.
Got it.
Hey, Dad.
Pack quickly. Young Master Gu is coming to pick you up.
You'll need to stay at the safe house for a few days.
I'm trusting you and Ren Ran to look after Ruo Jin.
Shh.
You're afraid Wang Wenhao will come after you for revenge?
Of course he'll come after me.
I have to prepare for the worst.
The police are hunting him everywhere.
I bet he wouldn't dare go to Premier Medical Hall.
But I don't want Ruo Jin to be scared in the slightest.
Actually, there's another possibility.
He'll try every way to flee North City and hide.
Didn't you just say it yourself?
As long as Wang Wenhao isn't brought to justice,
Xu Ruo Jin won't have a moment of peace.
If it's as you said,
and he's left North City,
wouldn't it be even harder to find him?
So what do you want to do?
We split up.
You use Gu Yuan's satellite tracking system
to track Wang Wenhao's movements.
We'll look for clues in the underground market.
Okay.
Go, hurry.
Thanks for your help.
Once I'm out of the country, I'll repay you.
You should thank your father.
He begged me for help before he died.
You once helped Ren Feifan.
Why?
There are no permanent friends,
only permanent interests.
He made me lose so much face
at the Meniersen Group.
Now he's my enemy.
Good. Straightforward.
But given my current situation,
I can only rely on you.
Once I reach your country,
the Wang Family has assets there.
I'll reward you handsomely.
Don't feed me empty promises.
I want the money I'm owed right now.
I, Wang Wenhao, never owe favors.
I'll wire the money to you now.
Arrange my escape route immediately.
I still have a few places to visit in North City.
This one, and this one too.
Ren Feifan, I sent you the location.
Gu Yuan is already heading there.
Hurry up.
I've got the location.
That's the run-down building where Xu Ruo Jin passed out.
The Wang Family's lair.
Wang Wenhao very likely went there.
Okay, you two be careful.
Mm.
He's right near you.
Okay, I'll look around.
There. Go.
Stop!
Get back here!
Stop chasing. You can't outrun a car.
Hey, Ning Le.
I'm sending you a license plate. Track where this car went.
Got it.
There's a police checkpoint up north.
He most likely won't go that way.
Let's call the police.
Not yet.
I'm afraid he's still trying to mislead us.
That would only trouble the police.
Let's tail him first.
Okay.
Ren Feifan, Gu Yuan.
We found that Wang Wenhao's overseas account
just wired a sum to Princess Xinai.
Why don't you go check on Xinai's side?
Okay, we're on our way.
Looks like this Princess Xinai
wants to play both sides for profit.
But it doesn't matter.
Anything money can solve
isn't really a problem at all.
Have a seat.
What did you want to see us about, Princess?
Before I leave North City,
there are a few things I'd like to say to you.
No need to look around, handsome.
Wang Wenhao isn't here.
You said you wanted to make a deal.
Name your price.
Before we make the deal,
I have a few heartfelt words to share with you.
I hope you can be a little patient.
I'm afraid I don't have much patience.
If there's no news of Wang Wenhao,
then I'll take my leave.
Ren Feifan.
I've traveled all around the world,
but I've never met anyone like you.
I resent that you don't take me seriously.
You defeated me,
but I admire you.
A healer has a kind heart, and a kind heart is invincible.
Neither Wang Wenhao nor I are any match for you.
Understood.
Where's Wang Wenhao?
Wang Wenhao asked me to pass on a message.
He killed your mother,
and you took his father's life.
Can't the feud between your families finally be settled?
Spare his life,
and he promises never to return to this country.
He'll disappear forever.
And what if I refuse?
I know Wang Wenhao paid you a huge sum.
As long as you hand him over,
I'll pay you double.